<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>

  <ThoughtDef>
    <defName>HD_DrankNaphtha</defName>
    <thoughtClass>Helodrace.Thought_Memory_HelodPersonalityDescription</thoughtClass>
    <durationDays>1</durationDays>
    <stackLimit>1</stackLimit>
    <modExtensions>
      <li Class="Helodrace.ThoughtDefExtension_HelodPersonalityDescriptions">
        <descriptions>
          <li>The foul oily smell filling my mouth scrapes sharply at my nerves. I am forcing it down, but I cannot keep my irritation under control.</li>
          <li>The taste is truly awful. But if we are going to survive, we have to endure even this filthy oily reek.</li>
          <li>The stench of oil is overwhelming. My whole mouth feels like it is burning, but if this is for my survival, it is nothing.</li>
          <li>The oily smell is making my stomach turn. It makes my blood boil that I always have to endure something this unpleasant.</li>
          <li>Ugh, that disgusting oily smell will not fade. Everyone else is drinking it quietly, so I should endure it too, but it is truly miserable.</li>
          <li>What a terrible smell. There is no other choice, so I will drink it, but it feels like my whole body is being caked in grease.</li>
          <li>I cannot show weakness in front of my comrades, so I force it down. If we overcome this stench together, that will be enough.</li>
          <li>Everyone around me must be enduring this oily smell too. I cannot be the only one making a scene and throwing up, so I grit my teeth and bear it.</li>
          <li>If we are not going to fall apart, we have to endure even this rotten oily smell. It is the minimum price for each of us doing our part.</li>
          <li>A weakling would have started complaining about this stench already. But my body is mine to look after. I just need to shut up and swallow it.</li>
          <li>To think I have to drink this foul oil just to survive. Complaining to others will not change anything, so I have no choice but to swallow it alone.</li>
          <li>I hate this terrible smell, but if I collapse, I will be a burden to the whole group. I just want to rinse this filthy taste out of my mouth.</li>
          <li>The smell hits like smoke from a bad day. I clench my jaw, swallow the panic, and force my body to obey.</li>
          <li>The oily burn drags old fear up from somewhere deep. I go quiet and let it pass over me until my hands stop shaking.</li>
          <li>The taste pulls me back to people coughing in the dark. I keep my eyes on the others, because nobody should face that alone.</li>
          <li>The reek opens a door I keep shut. I step away inside myself and hold the line from somewhere cold and distant.</li>
        </descriptions>
      </li>
    </modExtensions>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <label>oil smell in my mouth</label>
        <description>I drank naphtha. The oily smell will not leave my mouth.</description>
        <baseMoodEffect>-4</baseMoodEffect>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </ThoughtDef>

  <ThoughtDef>
    <defName>HD_EnjoyedRawBTX</defName>
    <thoughtClass>Helodrace.Thought_Memory_HelodPersonalityDescription</thoughtClass>
    <durationDays>1</durationDays>
    <stackLimit>1</stackLimit>
    <modExtensions>
      <li Class="Helodrace.ThoughtDefExtension_HelodPersonalityDescriptions">
        <descriptions>
          <li>The intense oily smell running down my throat slams hard into my brain. This thrilling discomfort is proof that I am alive.</li>
          <li>This awful, overpowering scent is filling my whole body with strength. With this momentum, I feel like I could break through any enemy.</li>
          <li>What a magnificent stimulus. Others would gag at this smell, but to me it is the finest fuel for waking every sense in my body.</li>
          <li>It was foul at first, but this harsh oily smell stirs the venom and catharsis hidden deep in my chest. It is not bad.</li>
          <li>Wow, that smell is incredible. Everyone else seems to be suffering, but somehow I like this sharp, stinging sensation.</li>
          <li>The acrid oily smell pierces my nose, but quietly savoring this powerful stimulus alone is its own small pleasure.</li>
          <li>Can you feel this thrilling rush? This energy is coursing through me so strongly that I want to share it with my comrades.</li>
          <li>Why does this oily smell that everyone else avoids excite me so much? I should hide it outwardly, but inside, the electric pleasure will not stop.</li>
          <li>I can clearly feel this harsh fuel moving through my body. There may be no better stimulant for keeping us alive.</li>
          <li>Anyone too weak to handle this oily smell should step aside. This fierce stimulus that sets my blood boiling is only for the strong.</li>
          <li>I do not care what the others think. It is enough that this intense, burning scent is filling my nerves.</li>
          <li>Others would call me mad, but the stimulus from this revolting smell is rather excellent. Thanks to it, I can keep moving without tiring for a while.</li>
          <li>The rush comes with an old flash of terror. I seize it, twist it into anger, and make it drive me forward.</li>
          <li>The fuel steadies me, but the memories underneath it are too loud. I keep my head down and breathe through the shaking.</li>
          <li>The burn wakes old fear, and I hate that others might feel it too. I need to make sure everyone stays on their feet.</li>
          <li>The relief is real, but so is the old dread behind it. I retreat inward and let the chemistry carry the rest.</li>
        </descriptions>
      </li>
    </modExtensions>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <label>enjoyed raw BTX</label>
        <description>I drank raw BTX compounds. The oily burn was exactly what I wanted.</description>
        <baseMoodEffect>6</baseMoodEffect>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </ThoughtDef>

  <ThoughtDef>
    <defName>HD_BugleChargeCommandMood</defName>
    <thoughtClass>Helodrace.Thought_Situational_HelodPersonalityDescription</thoughtClass>
    <workerClass>ThoughtWorker_Hediff</workerClass>
    <hediff>HD_BugleChargeCommand</hediff>
    <modExtensions>
      <li Class="Helodrace.ThoughtDefExtension_HelodPersonalityDescriptions">
        <descriptions>
          <li>The ear-splitting bugle blast forces me forward. I know I have to charge, but this forced slaughter is deeply unpleasant.</li>
          <li>The order has come. I have to lead the way for my comrades, but that mad bugle sound is squeezing my heart too tightly.</li>
          <li>Charge? Even without that noisy bugle, I would cut down my own enemy. This feeling of being driven toward death is the worst.</li>
          <li>I do not want to go. I do not want to die. But that damned bugle is forcing my body to move, and anger boils up inside me.</li>
          <li>The bugle is ringing out. Everyone is rushing forward, so I have to go too. Please, let no one die. I am scared.</li>
          <li>With that deafening bugle, everyone has started running wild. I am running because I have no choice, but I will look after my own life.</li>
          <li>It is the charge order. Follow me. I will not let any of us fall behind. If we face it together, we can break through this terrible pressure.</li>
          <li>The bugle shaking the battlefield has left me reeling. I am too scared to move, but I am swept along by my comrades and forced to run.</li>
          <li>That is the attack signal. If we want to come back alive, we have no choice but to charge into that hail of bullets. Stay calm and do my part.</li>
          <li>That damned bugle is tearing at my eardrums. Do not think you can push me into death. My life is mine to decide. Still, I will tear apart the enemies in front of me.</li>
          <li>That noisy bugle is forcing me forward. While the others become bullet catchers, I will find a way to survive on my own.</li>
          <li>A forced charge is foolish, but if I do not run to that racket, the comrades beside me will be in danger. I have no choice.</li>
          <li>The bugle rips open old battlefield terror. I bare my teeth at it and turn the panic into a command to move.</li>
          <li>The bugle makes the past crash over me. I fall silent, follow the line, and try not to let anyone see my hands shake.</li>
          <li>The bugle sounds too much like the moments before people die. I lock onto my comrades and run because they need me beside them.</li>
          <li>The bugle drags me back somewhere I never wanted to revisit. I move with the charge, but part of me has already gone distant.</li>
        </descriptions>
      </li>
    </modExtensions>
    <stages>
      <li>
        <label>ordered to charge</label>
        <description>The bugle's command is still ringing in my ears, pushing me forward before fear can catch up.</description>
        <baseMoodEffect>-3</baseMoodEffect>
      </li>
    </stages>
  </ThoughtDef>

</Defs>
